freeprizeclub.com 2004-10-09

# FreePrizeClub

|  | 

**Your Privacy Statement**

FreePrizeClub understands that you may have concerns about safeguarding your privacy on-line. The Privacy Statement that follows explains our views and practices concerning privacy, and how they may pertain to you as you make full use of our many offerings. This statement discloses the privacy practices for all Web sites located at the uniform resource locator [**http://www.freeprizeclub.com**](http://www.freeprizeclub.com/).

**Article 1. Collection of Personal Information from Site Visitors**

FreePrizeClub automatically collects and/or tracks (1) the home server domain names, IP address, e-mail addresses, type of client computer, and type of Web browser of visitors to FreePrizeClub's Web site, (2) the e-mail addresses of visitors that communicate with FreePrizeClub via e-mail, (3) information such as personal, financial or demographic information, knowingly provided by the visitor in on-line forms, registration forms, surveys, and drawing entries, and (4) information, either in the aggregate or user specific, on what pages visitors access.

**Article 2. Use of Personal Data Collected**

Personal data collected by FreePrizeClub will be used by FreePrizeClub for editorial and feedback purposes, for marketing and promotional purposes, for a statistical analysis of user's behavior, for drawing product development, for content improvement, to inform advertisers as to how many visitors have seen or clicked their advertisements, and to customize content and layout of FreePrizeClub's site. Names, e-mail addresses, and postal information collected may be added to FreePrizeClub's databases and used for future e-mails, mailings regarding site updates, new products and services, upcoming events, and status of orders placed online. Financial information collected may be used to check the user's qualifications for registration, and to bill the user for products and services.

Demographic and profile data collected is used to tailor the visitor's experience at our site, enabling us to present content we think they might be interested in. We use customer contact information to send the user information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners.

**Article 3. Disclosure of Personal Data to Third Parties**

FreePrizeClub reserves the right to post collected data on FreePrizeClub's Web site, or share, rent, sell, or otherwise disclose data it collects to third parties. Any third party to which FreePrizeClub shares, rents, sells, or otherwise discloses personal data will be carefully prescreened by FreePrizeClub, determined by FreePrizeClub to be reputable, and will use the personal data for marketing products and services which FreePrizeClub determines, in its sole judgment, that visitors might find of interest. FreePrizeClub will disclose to third parties information knowingly and voluntarily disclosed by visitors, or information in aggregate form.

Through the use of third party cookies, an advertiser will be electronically notified when visitors view or click on its advertisements. This site contains links to other sites and FreePrizeClub is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites.

**Article 4. Opt-Out Right**

We allow users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we voluntary request information about the visitor. This site also allows users to remove their information from our database. If a user removes his or her information from the FreePrizeClub database it will no longer be used by FreePrizeClub for secondary purposes, disclosed to third parties, or used by FreePrizeClub or third parties to send promotional correspondences to the visitor. Users can remove their information by sending an email requesting removal to [remove@FreePrizeClub.com](mailto:remove@freeprizeclub.com).

**Article 5. Access to and Ability to Correct Personal Data**

Upon request via e-mail, FreePrizeClub will provide to visitors a summary of any personal information retained by FreePrizeClub regarding the visitor. FreePrizeClub will only send personal records to the e-mail address on file for the visitor name associated with it. Visitors may modify, correct, change, or update their personal record or cause their personal record to be removed from FreePrizeClub's database. Visitors may change or modify information previously provided by contacting FreePrizeClub via an e-mail to support@FreePrizeClub.net.

Article 6. Collection of Personal Data from Children The information and services provided at FreePrizeClub's web site by FreePrizeClub, its affiliates, sponsors, and advertisers are not intended to be viewed by children under 13 years of age. All drawings offered at FreePrizeClub are open to United States residents 18 years or older only. FreePrizeClub will not knowingly permit a child to participate in a game, offering of a prize, or another activity. If a child wins a drawing, that child's entry will be voided, and another winner will be drawn.

Concerning visitors to its site that it knows are children under 13 years of age, FreePrizeClub maintains the following policies:

FreePrizeClub will not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 years of age without prior parental consent, which will include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity. Without prior parental consent, online information will only be used to respond directly to the child's request and will not be used for other purposes without prior parental consent.

In the event a child submits information to the FreePrizeClub Web site, the child must provide an e-mail address for the child's parent or guardian. Thereafter, FreePrizeClub will send an e-mail to the parent or guardian alerting them to the child's registration and providing instructions on how the parent can provide consent for the child to view the contents of FreePrizeClub, or how the parent could view or delete the child's registration, if so desired.

FreePrizeClub will not knowingly distribute to third parties any personally identifiable off-line contact information concerning children under 13 years of age without prior parental consent.

No information collected from children is knowingly used for any marketing or promotional purposes whatsoever, either inside or outside FreePrizeClub.

**Article 7. FreePrizeClub's Right to Contact User**

FreePrizeClub reserves the right to contact site visitors regarding account status and changes to subscriber agreements, privacy policy, or any other policies or agreements relevant to site visitors.

**Article 8. FreePrizeClub's Right to Change Privacy Policy**

FreePrizeClub reserves the right to change this policy at any time by notifying visitors of the existence and location of the new or revised privacy policy.  
  
---|---
